<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Project on </title>
    <link>https://www.biostatgen.org/categories/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Project on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.biostatgen.org/categories/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Population in Thailand</title>
      <link>https://www.biostatgen.org/post/population-in-thailand/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.biostatgen.org/post/population-in-thailand/</guid>
      <description>Inside story: From the very beginning of human existence one thing has always been constant and that is movement. Humans just like animals tend to move about a lot. They rarely stay in one particular region for so long. Its either they travel to other places to visit, for work purposes or to settle down. Migration is quite high in the human populace. Asia being the most populous continent on planet earth has a huge variation in ethnicity, language and gene make up of its population and the constant movement of people in and out of that region has made it complicated to trace the origin of the diversity in that region.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Capturing fine-scale structure</title>
      <link>https://www.biostatgen.org/post/capturing-fine-scale-structure/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.biostatgen.org/post/capturing-fine-scale-structure/</guid>
      <description>Inside story: Biologically, a population is a group of living organisms of the same species that are living together and have the capability of interbreeding. Evolutionary processes such as migration, natural selection etc., has overtime contributed to the variations in the gene makeup of individuals that makes up a particular population. Subpopulations are as a result of these variations that are present in genes of individuals of a population. Population studies have several importance among which are; Information gotten from population studies can be used to infer population history, also studying the population of a place can reveal predisposing factors of disease in that place and several others.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
